argen-teens.com 2008-12-17

# Argen-teens.com

Privacy Policy 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted to argen-teens.com. On some pages, you can purchase a Membership to argen-teens.com, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are name, age, email address, sexual orientation, etc. We use ccBill, Paycom, Payex, Commercegate and NetCash's third-party credit card processing services, who will obtain additional information such as your address, and credit card data.

Credit Card info:

NOTE! the credit card info that you submit on the signup forms are submitted direct to the credit card companies and are not even stored on our servers for security reasons. The signup pages are secure and encrypted and therefor impossible to hack.

The Way We Use Information:

The information collected by argen-teens.com is used solely for the creation and maintenance of your Membership account. WE DO NOT sell, loan, lease, swap, trade or otherwise disclose your personal data or email address. That information collected by ccBill, Paycom, Payexis, Commercegate, NetCash used for the purpose of processing payment of your Membership to argen-teens.com.

Our Commitment To Data Security:

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging on to the "My Page". We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

How To Contact Us:

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at support@argen-teens.com.
